{
    "subject": "resource/Little_Red_Riding_Hood's_Zombie_BBQ",
    "predicate": "property/developer",
    "object": "EnjoyUp",
    "human_readable": "Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ was developed by EnjoyUp.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9665143489837646,
            "question": "Who developed the game Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.803718090057373,
            "question": "Is there a popular fairy tale that Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ is based on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8027573227882385,
            "question": "Can you describe the theme of Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7898836731910706,
            "question": "Who might the target audience for Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7531736493110657,
            "question": "What is the name of the game development company behind Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7296481132507324,
            "question": "What type of game is Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7048168778419495,
            "question": "What might be some gameplay features in Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22150014340877533,
            "question": "What other games has EnjoyUp developed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07628263533115387,
            "question": "What are some popular zombie-themed games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.009630363434553146,
            "question": "How does the name of the game reflect its content?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ was developed by EnjoyUp.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3141_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular zombie-themed games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3141_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other games has EnjoyUp developed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3141_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some gameplay features in Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3141_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3141_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Developer: EnjoyUp\" and \"Developed by Spanish studio EnjoyUp,\" which confirms that the game \"Little Red Riding Hood\u2019s Zombie BBQ\" was indeed developed by EnjoyUp."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}